I'm guessing he bought her the big pipe organ...
我猜他给她买了个管风琴
...and she's really not happy about it.
而她很不喜欢那个
Daddy, I just... I can't marry him.
老爸 我就是无法和他结婚
I'm sorry.
对不起
I just don't love him.
我只是不爱他了
Well, it matters to me.
这对我很有关系
She should not be wearing those pants.
她真不应该穿那条裤子
I say push her down the stairs.
我觉得应该把她推下楼
Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs!
把她推下楼…
Come on, Daddy, listen to me!
爸爸 听我说
It's like all of my life, everyone's always told me, "You're a shoe!
这就好像在我一生中 所有人都告诉我: "你是鞋子 "
You're a shoe! You're a shoe! You're a shoe!"
"你是鞋子…"
Then today I stopped and said, "What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
然后今天 我停下来对自己说: "如果我不想成为鞋子呢？
What if I wanna be a purse? You know?
如果我想成为一个包包？
Or a hat?"
或一顶帽子？"
I don't want you to buy me a hat, I am a hat.
不 我不是要你给我买帽子 我是说我是帽子
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
这是个比喻 爸爸
You can see where he'd have trouble.
你看得出他哪里听不懂
Look, Daddy, it's my life.
爸爸 这是我的生活
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
也许我可以和摩妮卡住在一起
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
我猜我们已经确定 她要和摩妮卡住在一起了
Well, maybe that's my decision.
也许那是我的决定
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
也许我不需要你的钱
Wait! Wait! I said maybe!
等等 我说也许